[{"answer": "Hey, you, manager... Don't get any ideas, fucker... See that man there? I bark and he bites", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "My side, shit", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Thanks again, my friend", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It's okay.", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "But do you mean it?... But you just told him that if worse comes to worse..", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "But I want to know what you think", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You got kids", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Ah, I know!  You're being very cooperative.  I got no complaint against you whateve", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I don't care who you are...  I just want to get you outta here, safe, right", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " If you take anybody, please take me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm not alone", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I got my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "One word.  You won't find it in the phone book", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Call me whatever you want", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Okay, my friend, I want to see if the people in the bank are okay, then what I want to do is work out a way to get them out of there.  I want to come over there, without a gun... and you can frisk me.  So you can see you can trust me.  So we can talk and find a way outta this mess", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You frisk me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "To show that we're negotiating", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "All right... let's go", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " When I'm bein' fucked, I like to be kissed a lot.  Who the fuck are you tryin' to con me into some deal?  You're a city cop, where's the that place?  This is a federal offense, I got kidnapping, armed robbery, they're gonna bury me!  You know it, you can't talk for them, you're some flunky pig tryin' to bullshit me.  Now God damn it, get somebody in charge here to talk to me", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Calm down... look at this, look at him...", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Hey, my friend...  Sure", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Doing what", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I don't want to be paid.  I'm here with my friend and eight other people... and we're dyin'!  They're gonna blow our guts out, man!  You're gonna see our brains onna sidewalk!  How's that for all you shu", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Oh yeah?  Give up?  You ever been in prison", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You realize, my friend, that we're gonna get outta the country, so if you wanna talk to somebody, do it now... You gotta Mother or a Father? Friends?  If we gotta be outside the country, where do you wanna go?  Any country. Just name a country", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " that place... That's not out of the country", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, I'm not tryin' to fuck you", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I swear to God I had nothing to do with it..", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Because I'm scared, that's why. You never smoked", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You stopped?  Why", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Go ahead.  Do what you want to do. I hate to see you break a perfect record.  You oughta take care of your body", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Your body is the temple of the Lord", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "We're all set at that place", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He's totally unstable.  He'll make a mistake", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What makes you think you'll be able to control it", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "He hasn't so far.  I'm the one who can make a mistake.  That's what scares the shit out of me", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, my friend, these hostages are keeping me alive", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "At the airport.  We get on the plane, check it out, and if it's all okay we'll send them out.  Except one", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "At the airport.  We get on the plane, check it out, and if it's all okay we'll send them out.  Except one", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I want to talk to my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well... I'm out of the hospital", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I never thought I'd get out this way.  I'll tell you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You can't talk or do anything.  You really feel... you know... I'm just sort of coming out of it now", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah.  So how are you", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Fine, thank you.  I'm in trouble. That is... now I am", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't know what I'm gonna do... you know.  Boy... I'm dying", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Yeah... I know", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "What?  What are you talking about? You are dying?  Did you ever listen to yourself when you say that", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I don't know what I'm gonna do... you know.  Boy... I'm dying", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What are you talking about", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Where you gonna go", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Why you going to that place", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Huh... I don't know.  They got my friend's there.  I don't know why the fuck I'm going there for", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I know that.  I'm warped... I'm warped", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "All right.  Then what do you want me to say", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Where are they now?  Just tell me... are they on the phone now", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " That's great.  Just terrific.  You talk to me with them on the phone, right?  That is really smart.  And, you don't tell me", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You don't have a choice", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "No!  They're standing all around me. Seven thousand fucken cops... all around me", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Look... don't throw that on me", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Look... who's on the phone", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Who's on the phone, now?  What do you mean... throw it on you?  You knew it, right", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Thank you much... and huh, bon voyage", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Yeah... see ya in my dreams, huh", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Special to me, too", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Sure", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I said you were never a faggot", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "He was very understanding", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "For God's sake don't start in on my friend again..", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Mom.  Mom.  There are some things a mother shouldn't say in front of her son", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " Not now, Mom, please", "docId": "Dog-Day-Afternoon.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": " I can't, Mom.  If I come out my friend will kill them", "qsentId": 72}]